Lewis Nathaniel Chase Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- General File, 1836-1941 (Box 34-162)
  - London, England (Box 104)
    - 1910-1916, (10 folders) (Box 105)
  - Lonergan Stock Co., 1912-1913
  - Long, Huey Pierce, 1935
  - Los Angeles, Calif., map, undated
  - Loucks, R. F., undated
  - Louisville Courier Journal, undated
  - Lovelace, Richard, 1926
  - Low, Sidney, 1912-1915
  - Lowell, Amy, 1917-1926, 1935-1936
  - Lowrie, Vera S., 1923 (Box 106)
  - Lucas, Nell, undated
  - Lucas, E. V., 1929, 1938-1939
  - Lucey, R. M., 1920
  - Ludovic, Anthony, undated
  - Lunt, Carroll, 1925
  - Luskin, John, 1928-1932
  - Lyceum Bureau, 1914-1915
  - Lyceum club, 1911-1915, (4 folders)
  - Lyceum magazine, 1911-1912
  - Lynd, Robert, 1920-1929
  - Lynn, E. W., 1908, undated
  - Lyon, Lillian Bowes, 1937
  - Lysaght, S. R., 1936
  - “M” miscellaneous (Box 107)
    - Correspondence, 1907-1940
    - Miscellany, 1916-1937
    - Newspaper clippings, 1911-1940
  - Macaulay, Rose, 1917-1919, 1925, 1931
  - Macauley, Thomas B., 1899, 1907, 1927, 1935, (2 folders)
  - McCarty, Ruth D., 1918 (Box 108)
  - McFarland, C. L., 1928-1931
  - Mace, Sophia, 1930
  - McClellan, Clarence Stuart, 1931
  - McCord, David T. W., 1936-1940
  - McCormick, S. B., 1916-1917
  - McFee, William, 1922
  - McFie, T. G., 1935
  - McGinnis, Norah, 1929
  - MacKail, J. W., 1911, 1917-1928, 1938
  - Mackarness, H. J. C., 1932-1937
  - MacKaye, Percy, 1936-1938
  - Mackereth, James A., 1913
  - MacKenna, Stephen, 1934-1937
  - MacKinnon, Sallie Lou, 1928-1936
  - MacKintosh, E. A., undated
  - MacLear, Martha, 1934-1935
  - MacLeish, Archibald, 1933-1941
  - MacLeod, E. D., 1927-1928
  - MacLeod, G. Hamilton, 1910
  - MacManus, Seumas, 1938
  - McMillan, Margaret, 1924
  - MacNair, H. F., 1938-1939
  - MacNeice, Louise, 1937-1939
  - McNaught's Monthly, 1925
  - Madagascar, map, undated
  - Maddox, Emily, 1935
  - Male, Charles, 1932-1933
  - Malloch, G. R., 1923
  - Malone Society, 1910
  - Malory, Thomas, 1922, 1928
  - Malvran, undated
  - Mammoth Cave, Ky, undated (Box 109)
  - Manchester, Mary Elizabeth, 1933
  - Manicuring, undated
  - Mansfield, Katherine, 1920-1930, 1937,-1941
  - Manwaring, Wilfred H., 1906-1907
  - Maori, 1926
  - Maphis, Charles G., 1932
  - Maps, 1927-1934
  - Marco Polo, undated
  - Marketing articles, 1924-1925
  - Markham, Edwin, 1927, 1940
  - Marlowe, Christopher, 1921-1927, 1937-1940
  - Marquand, John P., 1937-1940
  - Marquis, Don, 1934-1939
  - Marriage, 1930
  - Marriage congratulations, 1906-1907
  - Marriage of Figaro, undated
  - Marsh, Edward, 1917-1919, 1939
  - Marshall, C. R., 1930-1937 (Box 110)
  - Marshall, George W., 1933-1937
  - Marshall, Lydia, 1935-1936
  - Chase, Martin, 1904-1913
  - Martin, Myra Belle, 1902-1937, (2 folders)
  - Marvell, Andrew, 1921, 1927, 1939
  - Marvin, Burdette K, undated
  - Marvin, Cloyd H., 1929
  - Marvin, Harvey, 1925-1937
  - Master's thesis, 1929, undated (Box 111)
  - Marx, Karl, 1926-1930
  - Masefield, John, 1910-1941, (2 folders)
  - Masefield, Muriel, 1927
  - Maskee, undated
  - Mason, Mrs. James M., 1933-1941
  - Mason, Thomas, 1927-1928
  - Massinger, Philip, 1939-1940
  - Matheson, Annie E., undated
  - Mathews, Elkin, 1918
  - Matthews, Brander, 1899, 1936
  - Masters, Edgar Lee, 1915, 1923-1938, (2 folders)
  - Mattress catalogs, 1913 (Box 112)
  - Maugham, W. Somerset, 1922-1925, 1932-1940
  - Maynard, Theodore, 1924, 1930-1938
  - Mayne, Ethel Colburn, 1923-1924, 1939-1941
  - Mears, Isabella, 1923
  - Meloney, Frank, 1924
  - Menken, Adah Isaacs, 1929-1934
  - Mencken, H. L., 1921-1940, (2 folders)
  - Mendel, Max, undated
  - Merchant, Frank, 1936-1937
  - Merchant Taylor's school, 1914
  - Meredith, George, 1903, 1913, 1928, 1937-1940
  - Merker, M., 1909-1911
  - Mermaid club, undated
  - Method in science of man, 1926
  - Mew, Charlotte, 1918
  - Meyer family, 1898-1914
  - Meyerstein, Edward H. W., 1936-1941
  - Meynell, Alice, 1911-1923, 1929, 1940-1941 (Box 113)
  - Middleton, Richard, 1922, undated
  - Middleton, Thomas, 1927
  - Milburn, Joseph Anthony, undated
  - Miles, Susan, 1920-1923, 1935, (3 folders)
  - Mill, John Stuart, 1925
  - Millay, Edna St. Vincent, 1922-1940, (2 folders)
  - Miller, Alberta, 1934-1935
  - Miller, Frank A., 1926
  - Miller, George R., 1935-1936
  - Milliken, Robert A., 1926, 1939
  - Mills and Boon, 1913
  - Milner, A., 1896
  - Milton, John, 1902-1904, 1924-1938
  - Mind, the growth of, 1921-1926
  - The miracle, 1927
  - Mirrorscope, 1910
  - Mitchell, Margaret, 1936-1937 (Box 114)
  - Mitchell, Susan, 1917
  - Modern languages, 1915
  - Modern Language Association, 1907-1917, 1930-1931
  - Mohammedanism, 1924-1936
  - Mohawk Club, 1930
  - Moliere, 1922
  - Mongolia, 1926
  - Monograms, undated
  - Monro, Harold, 1928-1933
  - Monroe, Harriet, 1926, 1935-1938
  - Monroe, Paul, undated
  - Montagu, Lady Mary Wortley, 1928
  - Moore, George, 1923-1939
  - Moore, Louis H., 1911-1914
  - Moore, M. E., 1912-1913
  - Moore, Marianne, 1925, 1935-1936
  - Moore, T. Sturge, 1925-1939
  - Morality play, 1903
  - Moran, Edward C., 1934-1936
  - More, Paul Elmer, 1921, 1929, 1935-1937
  - Morehead, Charles, 1929-1936
  - Moreland, John Richard, undated
  - Moritz, Florence, 1905-1906
  - Morley, Christopher, 1922, 1931
  - Morley, Lord, 1921
  - Mormonism, 1910-1911, 1933
  - Morrell, E. 1931-1933 (Box 115)
  - Morris Plan Co., 1928-1929
  - Morris, William, 1904-1919, 1927-1940, (2 folders)
  - Morrison, Mrs. Frank, 1926
  - Morton, E., 1906
  - Motherhood, 1906, (3 folders)
  - Mottos, undated
  - Moulson, George, 1910-1911, 1933-1935
  - Movies, 1926-1927
  - Muir, Edwin, 1925-1932, 1940
  - Mukerji, D. G., 1924-1925, 1932, 1938
  - Mullins, J., 1924
  - Muncy, Lysbeth, 1936
  - Munro, Hugh Hector, 1930
  - Murdock, John, 1933-1937
  - Murphy, D., 1908-1915
  - Murphy-Rowan, Inc., 1929
  - Murray, John, 1928
  - Murray, T. C., 1928
  - Murry, John Middleton, 1920-1940, (3 folders)
  - Music and the critic, 1924, 1932 (Box 116)
  - Music, modern, 1930
  - Music publishers, 1904-1906
  - Myers, Mamie Darling, 1934
  - Myers, Phoebe, 1912-1914
  - Mysticism, 1922-1928
  - Myths, 1922-1927
  - Mythology, 1907, undated
  - “N” miscellaneous
    - Correspondence, 1910-1916, 1929-1934
    - Miscellany, 1898, 1907, 1914, 1928-1937
    - Newspaper clippings, 1928, 1934-1938
  - Naidu, Sarojini, 1934-1937
  - Nance family, 1925-1936
  - Nathan, George, 1926, 1932
  - Nation, 1911, 1917, (2 folders)
  - National Home-Reading Union, 1928-1929
  - Nature and men, 1923-1928
  - Nearing, Scott, undated
  - Negro poets, 1924
  - Neidig, William J., 1917
  - Neihardt, John G., 1936-1940
  - Neilson, William Allen, undated
  - Nevin, Hardwick, 1918
  - Newbolt, Henry, 1912, 1932, 1939-1940 (Box 117)
  - Newburyport, Mass., undated
  - New Century Club, undated
  - New Castle, Del., 1934-1935
  - Newcastle, undated
  - Newell, Florence, 1912-1913, 1931-1932
  - Newman, Cardinal, 1899, 1906
  - New Players Society, 1913
  - New Victorian Club, 1911
  - Newspaper clippings, undated
  - Newspaper verse, 1904-1905, undated
  - New Statesman magazine, 1913, undated
  - Newspaper in binders, undated
  - New Republic, 1925
  - Newton, A. J., 1926
  - Newton and Co., 1927
  - New York, N.Y., undated
  - Nicoll, William Robertson, 1925
  - Nichols, Beverly, 1926
  - Nichols, Robert, 1917-1932, 1940
  - Nicholson, Meredith, 1906-1907, 1933-1934
  - Nietzsche, 1922
  - Nineteenth-century literature, 1898, 1906
  - Nobodies Club, 1912-1913
  - Nock, Albert J., 1934-1937
  - Noguchi, Yone, 1920-1922, 1937
  - Nollen, John S., 1905
  - Norris, John S., 1905
  - North Carolina, 1934-1936
  - North China Daily News, 1925
  - Not quite bright, 1926 (Box 118)
  - Novels, 1899-1911, 1917-1937, (2 folders)
  - Novelists, 1920, 1939
  - Now and then, 1926
  - Noyes, Alfred, 1922, 1928-1941
  - Noyes, Bertha, 1934-1935, undated
  - “O” miscellaneous
    - Correspondence, 1907, 1913-1915, 1924-1927
    - Miscellany, 1912, undated
    - Newspaper clippings, 1921-1924, 1934-1939
  - O'Brien, J. E., 1927-1930
  - O'Casey, Sean, 1934-1935
  - O'Connor, Frank, 1932-1940
  - Odets, Clifford, 1936-1939
  - Odier, Henri, 1910-1911
  - O'Faolain, Sean, 1928, 1937-1940
  - O'Flaherty, undated
  - Ogden, Charles W., 1934-1938
  - Ogilvie, Juliet, 1923-1924
  - O'Gorman family, 1912-1914
  - O'Grady, Standish, 1919
  - O'Henry, 1922, 1928-1939
  - Olp, E. E., 1925-1926
  - O'Neill, Eugene, 1923-1940 (Box 119)
  - O. P. Club, 1912
  - Open Forum Speakers Bureau, 1926
  - Opera, 1836, 1934, undated, (2 folders)
  - Orage, A. R., 1937
  - Orders, 1928
  - Oriental art, 1929-1933, undated, (2 folders)
  - Oriental poetry, 1930
  - Oriental religions, 1927
  - Orientalia lists, 1935-1939
  - Orleans, Duke of, undated
  - Osborne, John, Ball, 1913
  - Ostenso, Martha, 1924
  - Osteopaths, 1931
  - O'Sullivan, Seumas, 1926-1934, 1940
  - Otway, Thomas, 1926-1927
  - Ould, Hermon, 1931, 1936
  - Owens, C. Everard, undated
  - Oxenham, John, 1941
  - Oxford, England, boat race, 1911
  - Oxford Movement, 1925
  - Oxford, England, verse-speaking contest, 1926
  - “P” miscellaneous
    - Correspondence, 1906-1915, 1923-1940
    - Miscellany, 1906-1918, 1925-1940
    - Newspaper clippings, 1913, 1923-1936
  - Pacific Palisades, Calif., 1925-1926 (Box 120)
  - Painters, 1901-1902
  - Palaverers Club, 1934-1937
  - Palmer, Henry, 1934
  - Palmer, Morgan, 1925
  - Paper bag cooking, 1911
  - Paris, France, 1913, (6 folders)
  - Parker, Dorothy, 1936
  - Parks, Joe, 1925-1926
  - Parliament, 1911, (2 folders)
  - Parodies, 1921-1927
  - Pasadena, 1925-1931, (4 folders)
  - Passports, 1900, 1916-1927 (Box 121)
  - Patcher, Kenneth, 1936-1940
  - Pater, Walter, 1927, 1939
  - Patmore, Conventry, 1921
  - Patton, Marion, 1917-1918
  - Payne, Susie, 1912-1915
  - Peacock, Thomas Love, 1927
  - Pearse, Padaic, 1935
  - Peck, Elizabeth, 1936-1937
  - Peking, China, 1923-1932
  - Peking Club, 1921-1926
  - Peking Educational Supply Co., 1921-1925
  - Peking Institute of Fine Arts, 1921-1925
  - Pembroke College, Oxford University, Oxford, England. 1932
  - Pennell, Joseph, 1926-1930
  - Pennsylvania, 1935
  - Pennsylvania college trip, undated
  - National League of American Pen Women, 1933-1936
  - Pepys, Samuel, 1903-1906, 1934, undated
  - Perceval, Mina, 1911-1913
  - Perkins, Charles B., 1928-1930
  - Perkins, Clara H., 1917
  - Perry, William Gilmer, 1929
  - Persia, 1926-1927
  - Persian poet, Firdausi, 1933-1934
  - Personality in Science, 1925-1926
  - Pessimism, 1930
  - Peters Steamship Agency, 1927
  - Petitcol, Juliette, 1909-1914 (Box 122)
  - Petrarch, Franesco, 1908
  - Petrified forests, undated
  - Philippines, undated
  - Phillips, Mary E., 1916, 1926
  - Phillips, Stephen, 1903-1906, 1912, 1927, (2 folders)
  - Philology, undated
  - Philosophy, 1919, 1924, undated
  - Ph. D, Columbia University, New York, N.Y., 1903
  - Philputt, Grace M., 1909-1914
  - Photographs, 1918-1923, undated
  - Phrenology, 1890, 1906
  - Picot, Madame Marie, 1913-1914
  - Pi Gamma Nu, 1927
  - Pirandello, Luigi, 1927-1932, 1939
  - Pitt, D. G., undated
  - Pitter, Ruth, 1927, 1934-1939
  - Plato, 1928
  - Play Actors Society, 1912-1913 (Box 123)
  - Players, 1914-1915
  - Playgoing club, 1912
  - Pocahontas, 1927
  - Poe, Edgar Allen, 1915, 1941
  - Poker, 1928
  - Pollett, Geoffrey, 1936
  - Pomona College, Claremont, Calif., 1925-1927
  - Pond, J. B., 1914
  - Ponies, 1927
  - Ponsonby, Arthur, 1925-1928
  - Pope, Alexander, 1938-1939, undated
  - Porter, Alan, 1930
  - Post cards, 1932-1937, undated
  - Pound, Ezra, 1932-1941
  - Pound Louise, 1915
  - Powell, G. Harold, 1921
  - Powys, John C., 1934-1939
  - Prayers of Hariri, 1922
  - Pre-Raphaelitism, 1906, 1942
  - Press notices, 1925
  - Prescriptions, 1902-1914
  - Presbyterian Men's Club, 1926
  - Price, M. T. (Fidelia), 1934-1936 (Box 124)
  - Price, Thomas Randolph, 1901, 1934
  - Prices, autograph books, undated
  - Priestley, John B., 1927-1929
  - Prior, Matthew, 1940
  - Programs
    - 1899-1939, (6 folders)
    - 1912-1913, 1930-1941, undated, (5 folders) (Box 125)
  - Pronunciation of foreign words, undated (Box 126)
  - Prose, 1898, 1920-1928, (4 folders)
  - Providence, R.I., 1931-1935
  - Psi Upsilon, 1902, 1926-1937, (2 folders)
  - Psychological research, 1927, 1928
  - Publications, 1914
  - Publishers' catalogs, 1925-1929, 1941
  - Pyrography, 1904
  - Pamphlets and notes, Quakers, 1907-1911, undated
  - “Q” miscellaneous, 1913, 1929, undated
  - Queen Victoria, 1926, undated
  - Quennell, C. H. B., 1919
  - Quennell, Peter, 1922, 1932
  - Quill Club
    - 1909-1914, (3 folders)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 127)
  - Quinby, Ruth, 1913
  - “R” miscellaneous
    - Correspondence, 1907-1916, 1925-1939
    - Miscellany, 1930-1935, undated
    - Newspaper clippings, 1929-1936, undated
  - Race, 1930, undated, (2 folders)
  - Radio, poetry readings, 1927-1928, undated
  - Raffles, Sir Stamford, 1926
  - Railsback, 1926
  - Raine, Alice Chase, 1900, 1910, 1926-1941
  - Rainey, Ada, 1927-1940 (Box 128)
  - Raleigh, Walter, 1923-1926
  - Randall, John H., 1928
  - Ranelagh Club, 1914
  - Ransom, John Crowe, 1927, 1938
  - Rare books, 1929
  - Ray, Walter, 1921
  - Read, Herbert, 1928-1938
  - Reade, Charles, 1904, 1936
  - Reader, 1928
  - Reading, 1914-1929, (3 folders)
  - Receipts, medical, 1929, 1937
  - Recitations, 1902, 1923, (2 folders)
  - Redpath bureau, 1925
  - Reed, Langford, 1924, 1937-1939
  - Reimann, Franz, 1915-1916
  - Rejections, 1906-1910, 1918-1925, (3 folders)
  - Religion, 1925-1935
  - Renaissance, 1925
  - Renan, Ernest, 1923
  - Rendall, Vernon, 1914, 1930-1941
  - Reno, Nevada, 1932
  - Reprints, undated
  - Reputation be damned, undated
  - Research libraries, 1932-1933
  - Rice, Alice W., 1901, 1917, 1940, undated (Box 129)
  - Rice, Cale Young, 1917-1922, 1939-1940
  - Richardson, Dorothy, 1938, undated
  - Richelieu, prompt book, undated
  - Riding, Laura, 1928-1931, 1938-1939
  - Rittenhouse, Jessie B., undated
  - Rittenhouse, Joseph, 1936, undated
  - Riverside Junior College, Riverside, Calif.
    - 1925-1928, (5 folders)
    - 1926-1927, (6 folders) (Box 130)
  - Riverside Public Library, Riverside, Calif., 1911-1914
  - Riverside Library School, Riverside, Calif., 1926, (2 folders)
  - Robert College, Istanbul, Turkey, 1908-1909 (Box 131)
  - Roberts, Helen, 1926
  - Roberts, Martin A., 1936-1938
  - Robertson, James Alex, 1932-1934
  - Robinson, Edwin Arlington, 1916-1940, (3 folders)
  - Robinson, Helen A., 1911
  - Robinson, Lennox, 1927, 1939
  - Robinson, W., undated
  - University of Rochester, Rochester, N.Y., 1904, 1916-1918, 1939-1940
  - Earl of Rochester, 1930, undated
  - Rodker, John, 1930
  - Rogers, Eloise, 1926-1930
  - Rogers, Will, 1935
  - The Song of Roland, 1919
  - Romanticism, 1937-1938
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1934-1935
  - Root and branch, 1917
  - Rosenberg, Isaac, 1922
  - Ross, Ronald, 1928-1931
  - Rossetti, Dante Gabriel, 1907, 1928-1938
  - Rousseau, J. J., 1908
  - Rowe, Dorothy, undated
  - Rowe, Nicolas, 1929
  - Rowley, Richard, 1926-1933
  - Rowntree, H. S., 1915 (Box 132)
  - Royal Female Philanthropic Society, 1912-1913
  - Royal Geographic Society, 1914-1917
  - Royal Society of Literature, 1911-1914
  - Royster, Dean J. F., 1929
  - De la Ruelle, Madame Geubel, 1913
  - Rukeyser, Muriel, 1936-1940
  - Ruskin, John, 1911, 1919, 1928, 1933
  - Russell, Bertrand, 1922-1938
  - Russell, George William, 1914-1918, 1927-1940, (3 folders)
  - Russell, Charles Edward, 1930-1934, 1941
  - Russia, 1922-1929
  - Rylands, George, 1928-1932
  - “S” miscellaneous
    - Correspondence, 1905-1940
    - Miscellany, 1912-1913, 1925-1938, undated
    - Newspaper clippings, 1920-1940 (Box 133)
  - Sabin, Arthur K., 1917
  - Sackville, Margaret, 1913, 1928
  - Sackville-West, Vita, 1922, 1938-1939
  - Sainte-Beuve, 1926, 1937
  - St.. Emilson, 1899, undated
  - St. Germain de Lusignan, 1907
  - St. Patrick, 1928-1932, 1938
  - Saintsbury, George, 1922-1923, 1933
  - Salisbury, undated
  - Salvation Army Press, 1923-1928
  - Sampson, Martin Wright, 1895, 1906
  - Sandburg, Carl, 1920-1941
  - Benjamin H. Sanborn and Co., 1904-1905
  - San Francisco, Calif., undated
  - Sanskrit, 1930
  - Santayana, George, 1920-1940
  - Sappho, 1924 (Box 134)
  - Sargant, E. B., 1917
  - Sargent, Franklin H., 1896
  - Sark Island, 1927-1939
  - Sassoon, Siegfried, 1917-1941, (2 folders)
  - Satire, 1921-1932
  - Saturday Review, 1924-1926
  - Schauffer, Edward R., undated
  - Schauffer, Robert Haven, 1923
  - Schell, Sherrick, 1914-1916
  - Schenectady, N.Y., 1927-1930
  - Schenectady Woman's Club, 1928
  - Schiller, undated
  - Schools
    - 1902-1910
    - 1905-1909, (2 folders) (Box 135)
  - Schreiner, Olive, 1924
  - Schurz, Carl, 1904
  - Science discussions, 1925-1927
  - Scotland, 1911
  - Scott, Duncan Campbell, 1927
  - Scott, Sir Walter, 1921-1927, 1934-1938
  - Scott, Winfield, 1931, undated
  - Charles Scribner's Sons, 1928-1929
  - Scruggs, Anderson M., 1933-1940
  - Seabrook, 1925
  - Seaman, Sir Owens, 1918
  - Searight, Jeannette, undated
  - Sibilleau, Paul, 1907
  - Sedley, Charles, 1922-1928
  - Sedgwick, Anne Douglas, 1936
  - Segonzac, Paul, undated
  - Selfridge Co., 1910-1916
  - de Selincourt, Basil, 1918-1923, 1939-1941
  - Selleck, Willard Chamberlain, 1924-1926
  - Sellers, Frank H., 1931-1938
  - Semiramide, undated (Box 136)
  - Service, Robert W., 1936
  - Seton, Ernest Thompson, 1940
  - Servinhous, Leslie R., 1925
  - Sewanee Tennessee Press, 1906
  - Seymour, Whitney North, 1925-1933, undated
  - Shakespeare, William, 1917, undated, (2 folders)
  - Shaler, N. S., 1935
  - Shamel, A. D., 1927
  - Shanks, Edward, 1919-1925, 1938
  - Shanklin, Gertrude Avery, 1911-1913
  - Shannon, E. F., 1929
  - Sharp, Mrs. William, 1911, 1939, undated
  - Shaw, George Bernard
    - 1910-1914, 1926-1933, (5 folders)
    - 1909-1912, 1924-1939, (6 folders) (Box 137)
  - Shea, Michael F., undated
  - Sheldon, Doris M., 1936
  - Sherman, Stuart P., 1921-1925
  - Shewmake, Edwin F., 1929
  - Ships, undated
  - Shopping, 1914
  - Shute, G. P., 1912-1914
  - Sidgwick, Frank, 1927, 1934
  - Sidney, Maine, undated (Box 138)
  - Silhouette of Pearl-Adell Mikesell Chase, undated
  - Silvercruys, Suzanne, 1935
  - Simple Life exhibition, London, England, 1909-1911
  - Sims, George R., undated
  - Sinclair, James Huntly, 1926
  - Singleton, A. H., 1922
  - Siren, Osvald, 1920-1925, 1933
  - The Sisters' Tragedy, 1924
  - Slave with Two Faces, 1918
  - Sligo, 1927
  - Smart, Christopher, 1926-1929
  - Smith, Annie A., 1913-1916
  - Smith, C. Fox, 1917
  - Smith, Carrie W., 1906, 1913-1940, (2 folders)
  - Smith, Everett, 1928-1937 (Box 139)
  - Smith, Henry Clark, 1929-1937
  - Smith, Muriel, 1926, 1932-1940
  - Smith, William C, 1929
  - Smoke Magazine, 1932-1937
  - Smollett, Tobias, 1902, 1921-1925, undated, (2 folders)
  - Snare of catch words, undated
  - Snell, Isabelle Cromwell, 1933-1938
  - Snow, Wilbert, 1928-1940
  - Socialism, 1927-1933
  - Society verse, 1899-1903
  - Solomon Islanders, 1926
  - Sorley, W. R., 1920, undated
  - South American cruise, 1936-1937
  - Southernette magazine, 1904
  - Southold Savings Bank, N.Y., 1905-1916
  - Spain, undated (Box 140)
  - Spanish-French University Relations, 1908-1910
  - Spearing, Edna Mead, undated
  - Simplified Spelling Board, 1908-1911
  - Spencer, A. Beckwith, 1912-1914
  - Spender, Stephen, 1929, 1936-1939
  - Spengler, Oswald, 1928-1936
  - Spenser, Edmund, 1898, 1924
  - Spingarn, Joel Elias, 1901-1912, 1924-1939, (2 folders)
  - Spirit of the French Revolution, 1894
  - Spitteler, Carl, 1927
  - Squire, J. C., 1917-1927, 1938-1939
  - Squirrel Island, 1889, 1895, 1911, 1921, 1927, (3 folders)
  - von Stael-Holstein, Baron Alexander, 1923
  - Staelin, Richard, 1935-1936
  - Stage, 1892-1900, 1923, 1939
  - Stanford, Leland, 1932 (Box 141)
  - Stanford University, Stanford, Calif., 1893, 1915, 1930-1934
  - Stanton, Frank L., 1927
  - Stanton, Roger, 1926
  - Stapfer, Paul, 1901, 1910-1913
  - Starbuck, Victor, 1933-1938
  - State, 1926-1927
  - Steele, Dobson, 1904, undated
  - Steffens, Lincoln, 1937
  - Stein, Gertrude, 1929-1940
  - Stephens, James, 1916-1917, 1925-1940
  - Stephens, Leslie, 1906
  - Sterling, George, 1914, 1926-1940, (3 folders)
  - Stern, G. B., 1936
  - Stevens, F. W., 1925
  - Stevens, Wallace, 1936-1938
  - Stocker, R. Dimsdale, undated
  - Stockley, Cynthia, 1913, 1936
  - Stoddard, Lothrop, 1935
  - Stokes, Adrian, 1925 (Box 142)
  - Stokes, Frederick A., 1927
  - Strachey, John St. Loe, 1926
  - Strauss, 1922
  - Strauss, Samuel Wolf, 1923-1924
  - Strong, L. A. G., 1939-1941
  - Strut and Fret, 1907
  - Stuart, Jesse, 1934-1941
  - Stuart, Muriel, 1922-1927, 1936, undated, (2 folders)
  - Student papers, 1922, 1932
  - Sturgis family, 1908-1910
  - Suckow, Ruth, 1926
  - Sullivan, Mark, 1926
  - Superstition, 1920-1924
  - Sutcliffe, Ruth, 1932-1934
  - Swedish literature, 1926
  - Swinburne, Charles Algernon
    - 1906-1915, 1930-1939, (4 folders)
    - 1903-1937, (11 folders) (Box 143)
    - 1903-1937, (8 folders) (Box 144)
    - 1905-1928, 1938-1940, undated, (11 folders) (Box 145)
  - Swinnerton, Frank, 1932-1941 (Box 146)
  - Switzerland, undated
  - Synge, John M., 1931-1935
  - “T” miscellaneous
    - Correspondence, 1904-1915, 1929-1940
    - Miscellany, 1911-1912, 1927-1932, undated
    - Newspaper clippings, 1933-1938
  - Taggard, Genevieve, 1935-1938
  - Tagore, Rabindranath, 1913, 1919-1931, 1937-1939, undated, (3 folders)
  - T. P.'s Weekly, 1903-1905
  - Tasso, 1899, 1908
  - Tate, Allen, 1936-1938
  - Tattooing, 1925
  - Taylor, Edward, 1936-1939
  - Taylor, Robert (Lillian), 1936-1938
  - Taylor, Major Thomas (family), 1933-1935
  - Tchehov, Anton, 1923-1928
  - Teachers agencies, 1905-1909, 1929, (5 folders)
  - Teachers College Record, 1907, undated
  - Teachers, unemployed, 1930
  - Teaching of English, 1907 (Box 147)
  - Teasdale, Sara, 1924, 1933-1937
  - London Telephone Service, London, England, 1910-1914
  - Temple, undated
  - Tennant, E. Wyndham, 1919, undated
  - Tennessee, and Kentucky, 1907
  - Tennis, 1889, 1902, 1909-1916, 1923, (2 folders)
  - Tenney, C. W., 1928, 1934
  - Tenney, Ruth, 1936
  - Thames, 1911, undated
  - Thayer, Janet, 1912
  - Theatre, 1922-1930
  - Theobald, 1906, 1938
  - Thermidor, undated
  - Thomas, Augustus, undated
  - Thomas, Dorothy, 1931
  - Thomas, Edward, 1926-1939
  - Thompson, Edward, 1922-1939
  - Thompson, Francis, 1907, 1914, 1927, 1933
  - Thompson, Marietta B., 1911-1912
  - Thurlow, Lord, undated (Box 148)
  - Tibet, 1923-1934
  - Tickell, A. Phillips, undated
  - Ticknor, Caroline, 1937
  - Tietjens, Eunice, 1935-1938
  - Tiffany and Co., 1907-1912
  - Tilton, Mrs. William, 1936-1938
  - New York Times, 1902-1906
  - Titanic (steamship) disaster, 1912
  - Titus, Pauline Louise, 1917
  - Todhunter, John, 1927
  - Toga, Olga Fischer, 1922
  - Tolstoy, Leo, 1924-1925, 1933
  - Toller, Ernst, 1934-1939, (2 folders)
  - Tombo Jr., Rudolf, 1908-1913
  - Tomfool, Esq., 1923
  - Touring Club of France, 1911-1912
  - Toynbee, Arnold J., 1926
  - Towne, Charles Hanson, 1917, 1939, undated
  - Tragedy, 1915, 1927, 1940
  - Traherne, Thomas, 1909, 1935
  - Trial, Alphonse (family), undated
  - Traill, Henry D., undated
  - Training for foreign service, 1925-1926, undated
  - Transition Magazine, undated
  - Travel Magazine, 1882, 1911-1913, 1921-1931, (3 folders) (Box 149)
  - Travers, Pamela, 1935, 1941
  - Treat, Payson J., 1921
  - Trench, Herbert, 1916-1924, 1936, undated, (2 folders)
  - Trent, W. P., 1906
  - Trevelyan, Robert C., 1917, 1926-1928, 1937-1941
  - Triana, Gertrude de Perez, 1914
  - Tristram, 1928-1938
  - Turner, John Kenneth, 1922
  - Turner, Hugh (family), 1909-1911
  - Turner, Nancy Byrd, 1937-1940